Finding Aid for the Synanon Foundation Records LSC.0342
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Development Files
  - SRI - Carlos Patterson through Wire [transcripts]. (Box 13)
- Early History and Interviews
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Special equipment will be required for viewing. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Tapes and transcripts; Gift., ca. 1970. (Box 1)
- Exeter
  - Adult Education
    - Legal massive dose group log through Havasu High School - apprenticeships. (Box 443)
    - Education - high school - through Education reports - to Ellen Burke -, 1981 1981. (Box 444)
    - Moral judgement interview - Form A1 - standard scoring manual through ATC., 1977 (Box 445)
    - Monthly report - Joe McNamee & Sandy Higgins- through Unicept book on Walter's weekend -, 1977 August 1979. (Box 446)
    - Seminar report from log through Corporal punishment logs. (Box 447)
  - Linda Kaiser - Education
    - Psychology today article through Reaches and massive doses. (Box 373)
    - Western Psychological Association through Operation Excess LWB. (Box 374)
    - Research - changing partners through The Carnegie Corporation. (Box 375)
    - Foundations - LWB through Chicago., 1973 (Box 376)
    - Energy auditing course through Research testing correspondence -, 1974. (Box 377)
    - Executive manual through Games - Bank Ace, shopping bag, Big Deal, Cutting Corners. (Box 378)
    - Science experiments through Fundamentals of math - computer software. (Box 379)
    - First aid through Porterville - master test copies. (Box 380)
    - Porterville - answer sheets through Pre-algebra tests and objectives. (Box 381)
  - Office of Education
    - History of Western Civilization - 2 through Synanon correspondence and memos -, 1975. (Box 326)
    - Algebra - Geometry through English mechanics. (Box 327)
    - Exams through Science. (Box 328)
    - Mathematics massive dose through Ellen Delgado - school - TBA. (Box 329)
    - Finishing school through Education - lists from Books of lists -, 1979. (Box 330)
    - Miscellaneous education through Joi Chron - file information. (Box 330)
    - Education - lists - from Books of lists - through Boys - girls corps course descriptions - academic year., 1980 1975 (Box 331)
    - Eileen Rost chron - file - through Janie Tent / Terri Haberman chron -, September 7, 1976 - December 7, 1976 April 1-6, 1976. (Box 332)
    - Jarrie Tent / Terri Haberman chron through Irene Mckenna chron file -, June-August 1976 April-June 1975. (Box 333)
    - Linda Mellstein chron file - through Jarrie Tent chron file -, September-November 1976 April-June 1975. (Box 334)
    - Synanon school quarterly attendance reports - through [OVERSIZE BOX]., 1979 (Box 432)
    - punk Title I testing through 1976 - testing evaluations. (Box 451)
    - Scoring evaluations - through Scoring evaluations -, 1978 1982. (Box 452)
    - Scoring records - through College entrance examination boards (1 of 2)., 1981 (Box 453)
    - College entrance examination boards (2 of 2) through, July-September 1975. (Box 454)
    - October-December 1975 through 1971, 1975-1978. (Box 455)
    - Education file index through Masters evaluation forms - 2d quarter - 1978, 1975-1978. (Box 447)
    - Masters (employees) - SAF - through Reed-Tesser, Barbara - SAF-1977-1978, 1979 1975-1978. (Box 448)
    - Three year review through ITA Journal (1978) -, 1975-1978. (Box 449)
    - Accredidation - primary & secondary schools (1 - 12) - through MAZE/Guin COC -, 1976 1975-1978. (Box 450)
    - Measurement and evaluation through Kidsnatchers -, 1979. (Box 451)
    - 1979 chairman's conference - education report - Steve Haberman through Education - Kerhonkson - education proposal - (Box 433)
    - Education - job descriptions - schools - through 12-15 - San Francisco, 1979 -, 1979 1979. (Box 434)
    - 12-15 - Tomales Bay, 1979 through Lynn Ritter, Linda Millstein - chron file - February 15-March 31, 1976 - 1979. (Box 435)
    - Supply correspondence through Children's personality questionaires & materials-, 1979. (Box 436)
    - Academic testing - 1979 through March-April lower school daily log - (Box 437)
  - Synanon School -, 1980-1988
    - Education - reports from Ellen Burke - 1981 through Outcard - education reports -, 1986-1989. (Box 437)
    - Education - reports - general - through Education files - transcripts -, 1982- 1986. (Box 438)
    - Education - file index - 1979 through Upper school COC notes - (Box 439)
    - MAZE change of cube - through Controller., 1979 (Box 440)
    - Letters from children - through Medical consent forms., 1977 (Box 441)
    - Quarterly education reports - through Young people's game notes., 1980 (Box 442)
    - Havasu High School - general info through Young people's reports re school in Havasu. (Box 443)
    - Education - miscellaneous through Chart of accounts. (Box 371)
    - Education - cash disbursement records - Synanon School through Worksheets completed (folder 2 of 2). (Box 372)
    - Stock requisitions through Chron - managers desk - Rod Mullen and Jarrie Tent -, July-September 1974. (Box 365)
    - Girls corps correspondence - through Outgoing correspondence, May-July 1974 January-April 1973. (Box 366)
    - Santa Monica School - correspondence - through SIDS 1972., 1973-1974 (Box 367)
    - Medical consent forms for minors through High school - general info -, 1973. (Box 361)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence - through Outcard - files pulled for IRS case, 1974-1975 1982. (Box 362)
    - Synanon School - CED Master Library through From audio Brandon films. (Box 363)
    - Rise of the free school - copy 1 through Second quarter - Younger's language logs., 1980 (Box 364)
    - Animal husbandry - training through Visual training correspondence. (Box 365)
    - Hatchery Notes - through Hatchery reports., 1974 (Box 368)
    - Contract inquiries - through Oakland school - prospective kids in school -, 1976 1969-1971. (Box 369)
    - School - Oakland School through Oakland child custody -, 1973. (Box 370)
    - Jarrie Tent chron file - through Miscellaneous correspondence -, January-March 1975 May-June 1975. (Box 335)
    - T.N. Middle School - course description through S.M. course description 4-12 yrs, 1973-75 1974-75. (Box 335)
    - Curriculum S.M. Lower School through Job descripts., 1975 (Box 336)
    - Synanon tools - currency training through school - cube change - notes and logs., 1977 (Box 337)
    - Millstein chron - through Lower school, January 1972-February 1978 1978. (Box 338)
    - Lower School yard project through Lower School daily log. (Box 339)
    - Tower School daily info log - through Skin - Notes., May-August 1977 (Box 340)
    - TB Lower School through Lower School - cube change notes -, 1976 January 1976-January 1977. (Box 341)
    - Education - assistant registrar 1980 through Outcard - Ellen Delgado - 1980 chron -, May 9, 1985. (Box 351)
    - Synanon School - apprenticeships - high school second quarter 1981 through Education - Havasu guardianships 1980-1981. (Box 351)
    - Education - clothing - through Guin Huot - change of cube., 1980 (Box 352)
    - Graduation through Graduate project - Synanon School. (Box 353)
    - Education - curriculum - third quarter apprenticeships - through Outcard - reports - - Ellen Delgado., 1980 1980 (Box 354)
    - TB School - California State and Margin County Department of Education through TB School - course forecast first and second quarter - office of education., 1980 1980 (Box 355)
    - Education - curriculum - Synanon School first quarter - through Training course number 2 -, 1980 1976. (Box 356)
    - Course descriptions corps - through Education - Curriculum - third quarter - - Synanon School., 1978-1979 1980 (Box 357)
    - Office of Education - curriculum - strip school through School classes - Naomi Crawford (copies)., 1980 January 1977-July 1978 (Box 358)
    - School classes - Naomi Crawford (originals) through Miscellaneous., January 1977-July 1978 (Box 359)
    - Steve Marks through Jarrie Tent job -, 1975. (Box 360)
    - Lower School chron file - through Application - children., October 1977-January 1976 (Box 342)
    - C. Benton outgoing correspondence through Corps - interface, 1977 1977. (Box 342)
    - Corporal punishment through Terri Haberman - outgoing correspondence., January-December 1977 January-March 1977 (Box 343)
    - Crawford v. Crawford custody case through Lower development COC notes, 1979 1977-1980. (Box 344)
    - Lower development COC news through Upper development daily logs, January-April 1977 October 1977. (Box 345)
    - Lower school - lower development COC notes - video equipment through Massive doses - Synanon - Tomales Bay School, 1977 April 10, 1977 1978 1980. (Box 346)
    - School (2 - 12 year olds) SAF - through Outcard - daily logs - corps, 1978 1980. (Box 347)
    - Daily logs - upper school through TB School - personnel-, 1980 1980. (Box 348)
    - Education - personnel through Education - chron Ellen Delgado -, 1979-1980 1980. (Box 349)
    - Office of education - Ellen Delgado - personal - through Synanon School apprenticeships - high school first quarter, 1980 1981. (Box 350)
- Film (to eventually be deleted)
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Outcard - vol.20 - IRS religion - document to Janet Lejower; Outcard - 2 religion notebooks - to Jim Law. (Box 567)
  - Synanon on film -, April 1972. (Box 716, Item 21)
  - Wedding & newcomer explosion - orig. - outs - pic. -, 1971. (Box 568)
  - Governor Miliken at Detroit House -, 1970. (Box 568)
  - October newsreel, 1971. (Box 568)
  - Badger - Synanon in the Sierras - w.p. - outtakes - pic. 16mm color -, 1972. (Box 568)
  - Quest for freedom. (Box 568)
  - Legal suit - orig. - pic., November 1972. (Box 716, Item 22)
  - Professional weekend - orig. & w.p. - pic., 1972. (Box 568)
  - Tomales construction - orig. (Box 719, Item 21)
  - Halloween party -, 1972. (Box 719, Item 20)
  - Children of Synanon - duplicate. (Box 568)
  - Birth of a calf - Original & W.P. - 16 mm mag. music track - pic. -, 1971. (Box 568)
  - Boom - orig. and w.p. - outtakes - pic. -, 1972. (Box 569)
  - Boot camp - orig. - outs - pic. -, 1972. (Box 569)
  - To slay a white horse. (Box 569)
  - Tanker - orig. and w.p. - outtakes - pic. -, 1972. (Box 569)
  - San Francisco anniversary - w.p. - outs - pic. -, 1972. (Box 569)
  - Badger Synanon in the Sierra - w.p. - outtakes - pic. 16mm color -, 1972. (Box 569)
  - Female boots - orig. - outs - pic. - (1 of 2)., 1972 (Box 569)
  - Happy birthday C.E.D. - w.p. - outs - pic. -, 1972. (Box 569)
  - Synanon wedding festival titles. (Box 576, Item 19)
  - [Untitled 8mm film ca. 1965], 1980. (Box 576, Item 20)
    General
    Film content is of an explicit sexual nature.
  - [Untitled film]. (Box 569)
  - Female boots - orig. - outs - pic. - (2 of 2)., 1972 (Box 569)
  - Jitney unch - orig. - outs - pic. -, 1972. (Box 569)
  - Crawford wedding -, 1967. (Box 570)
  - School - orig. - pic., 1971. (Box 717, Item 6)
  - Instant guide to Synanon (4 of 4). (Box 720)
  - [Untitled film]. (Box 720)
  - [Untitled film]. (Box 720)
  - Swimming slobs - orig. and w.p. - outs. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 570)
  - San Francisco anniversary - orig. - outs - pic., 1972. (Box 570)
  - Mobile dental unit - orig. - outs pic. -, 1972. (Box 570, Item 10)
  - Synanon on film -, December 1972. (Box 717, Item 13)
  - Instant guide to Synanon (2 of 4). (Box 720)
  - Instant guide to Synanon (1 of 4). (Box 720)
  - Professional weekend - w.p. - outs. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 570)
  - Synanon wedding festival - through 1972. (Box 720, Item 16)
  - Behind the scenes of Synanon. (Box 720, Item 9)
  - Instant guide to Synanon. (Box 720)
  - Instant guide. (Box 570)
  - Children of Synanon (n.d.). (Box 570)
  - Children of Synanon - 1968. (Box 570)
  - The wedding festival. (Box 570)
  - Synanon wedding festival. (Box 570)
  - Synanon the people ranch - 1972. (Box 570)
  - Synanon on film -, August 1972. (Box 720, Item 14)
  - Instant guide to Synanon (3 of 4). (Box 720)
  - Ski trip Badger - w.p. - pic. -, 1973. (Box 571)
  - Ski trip Badger - orig. -, 1973. (Box 571)
  - NBC film mosquitoes -, 1971. (Box 571)
  - Hatchery - 4H - dental - music track. (Box 571)
  - Reno House - Cronkite -, 1966. (Box 571)
  - Steven Allen clip -, 1962. (Box 717, Item 14)
  - Instant guide to Synanon. (Box 571)
  - The Synanon Cure - w.p. - outs. - pic. -, 1971. (Box 717, Item 7)
  - Filthy McNasty -, 1971. (Box 717, Item 17)
  - Hatchery - 4H - dental - voice track. (Box 717, Item 9)
  - Let's make a movie -, 1971. (Box 571)
  - Synanon Detroit House. (Box 571)
  - Dance footage -, 1962. (Box 571)
  - Camp Badger. (Box 717, Item 23)
  - Steven Allen clip -, 1962. (Box 717, Item 18)
  - Synanon wedding -, August 6, 1972. (Box 571)
  - Synanon on film -, April 1973. (Box 717, Item 4)
  - Hut & chet test - Mag. TK. (Box 571)
  - The creative cube -, 1973. (Box 717, Item 8)
  - Interview with Jack Hurst - original. (Box 571)
  - The mighty Columbia River. (Box 571)
  - School. (Box 715, Item 7)
  - Women - voice track -, 1972. (Box 572)
  - To slay a white horse -, 1964. (Box 572)
  - Cartridge 2 - newsreel. (Box 572)
  - Del March Club and facilities. (Box 572, Item 22)
  - Del March Club - pre-Synanon -, 1958. (Box 715, Item 10)
  - CBS news clip - no sound -, 1961. (Box 572)
  - Synanon on film -, March 1972. (Box 572)
  - Synanon on film -, August 1972. (Box 572)
  - Synanon - color. (Box 572)
  - Footage of ranch and bay. (Box 715, Item 16)
  - Beauty contest at Del March club -, 1972. (Box 715, Item 5)
  - Behind the scenes at Synanon -, 1964. (Box 572)
  - Nevada State Prison. (Box 715, Item 13)
  - Synanon on film -, December 1972. (Box 715, Item 14)
  - Or die. (Box 572)
  - Group picture. (Box 715, Item 6)
  - Chester's arrival. (Box 715, Item 17)
  - Seawall. (Box 715, Item 19)
  - Stew demonstration. (Box 715, Item 8)
  - Newcomer auditions. (Box 572)
  - Building dam -, 1971. (Box 715, Item 18)
  - The Synanon cure - silent. (Box 715, Item 15)
  - A Synanon film -, 1972-1973. (Box 573)
  - Garrett lecture #2 - orig. - pic., 1973. (Box 573)
  - Synanon - Oakland. (Box 573)
  - Synanon on film - main title. (Box 573)
  - Synanon history lecture #1 - work print - pic. -, 1973. (Box 573)
  - Santa Monica wedding - orig. - pic. -, 1973. (Box 573)
  - Upward mobility - orig. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 573)
  - Bay to breakers - w.p. - pic., 1973. (Box 573)
  - Instant guide - orig. - master material -, 1973. (Box 573)
  - Portrero Hill. (Box 574)
  - 10th year anniversary celebration -, 1968. (Box 574)
  - Wedding festival - orig. roll #2 - pic. -, 1973. (Box 574)
  - Synanon Foundation - wedding tests. (Box 574)
  - Badger in the Sierras -, 1973. (Box 574)
  - Wedding festival -, 1973. (Box 574)
  - Instant guide -, 1973. (Box 574)
  - Wedding / the hatchery - orig. -, 1972. (Box 574)
  - Children of Synanon -, 1968. (Box 575)
  - Synanon on film -, April 1973. (Box 575)
  - Synanon commercial #1 (2 of 2). (Box 575)
  - Synanon commercial #1 (1 of 2). (Box 716, Item 10)
  - Behind the scenes at Synanon (2 of 2). (Box 716, Item 9)
  - Behind the scenes at Synanon (1 of 2). (Box 575)
  - Camera & film tests - color -, August 1972. (Box 575)
  - Hatchery - outtakes -, 1972. (Box 716, Item 5)
  - Promenade and ceremony. (Box 716, Item 7)
  - Instant guide to Synanon (2 of 2). (Box 575)
  - Instant guide to Synanon (1 of 2). (Box 575)
  - Synanon's people ranch. (Box 575)
  - Synanon Oakland and Tomales Bay -, 1970. (Box 716, Item 4)
  - Synanon people ranch. (Box 575)
  - Synanon the people ranch. (Box 716, Item 16)
  - Synanon wedding festival -, 1972. (Box 575)
  - Synanon, the people ranch -, 1972. (Box 716, Item 20)
  - Children of Synanon (1 of 2). (Box 575)
  - Children of Synanon (2 of 2). (Box 575)
  - Children of Synanon. (Box 716, Item 19)
  - B & w - strangers - children at play - swimming. (Box 576)
  - [Untitled - 2 small reels in one container]. (Box 576)
  - Synanon basic training #19. (Box 717, Item 7)
  - Synanon basic training #14. (Box 717, Item 6)
  - B & w outtakes - not viewed. (Box 576)
  - B & w outtakes - not viewed #2. (Box 576)
  - Flag ceremony at Candlestick Park in S.F. - 100 Synanon people -, July 4, 1976. (Box 576)
  - Synanon basic training #20. (Box 717, Item 8)
  - Synanon basic training #11. (Box 717, Item 11)
  - Synanon basic training #8. (Box 717, Item 10)
  - Synanon basic training #1. (Box 576)
  - Instant guide #2. (Box 576)
  - Synanon wedding festival. (Box 576)
  - Synanon law lecture #2 - Dan Garrett - master 16mm - - reels 1 & 2., 1973 (Box 576)
  - People ranch - master A-roll - orig. pic. - black and white -, 1972. (Box 576)
  - Synanon basic training #13. (Box 717, Item 9)
  - Outtakes - black and white - not viewed. (Box 576)
  - Red Room report #1 - orig. - pic. - trims & outtakes - 1973. (Box 577)
  - Music tape - Synanon seen #1 - Oakland -, November 6, 1971. (Box 577)
  - Wedding festival - master material - mag tracks 1 & 2 -, 1972. (Box 577)
  - Synanon on film - April - mag track & work print - master material -, 1972. (Box 577)
  - Wedding festival - master first answer print - 16mm -, 1972 (Box 577)
  - Wedding sound track C. (Box 577)
  - Wedding sound track B. (Box 577)
  - Red Room tests - orig. - pic & mag trac - 16mm. - black and white -, 1973. (Box 577)
  - Wedding sound track A. (Box 577)
  - Synanon lecture series - cutaways audience - orig. - outs - black and white -, 1973. (Box 718, Item 5b)
  - Instant guide - w.p. - outs - black and white & color -, 1973. (Box 578)
  - KTVU commercial - outtakes & trims - pic. -, 1973. (Box 578)
  - Badger - title w & without - copy[right] 1973 - pic. - orig. (Box 578)
  - Synanon - lecture #1 - D.D. Harvey - orig. - outs - black and white -, 1973. (Box 718, Item 10d)
  - Wedding festival - orig. - outs - roll #3 - pic. - 16mm - color -, 1973. (Box 578)
  - Instant guide - w.p. - color & black and white - live action - trims & outtakes -, 1973. (Box 578)
  - Instant guide - orig. - outtakes - live action rolls 1 & 2 -, 1973. (Box 578)
  - Footage of Oakland dining room & living room. (Box 718, Item 8)
  - Pete Harvey - Synanon history lec. #1 - audience pic & track - outtakes -, 1973. (Box 578)
  - Charlie Hamer - orig. - orig. pic. -, 1972. (Box 579)
  - Magic - flute - video to film - orig. - 16mm. - black and white -, 1973. (Box 579)
  - Bay to breakers - orig. - pic. - 16mm. - black and white -, 1973. (Box 579)
  - Trip - orig. & work print. (Box 579)
  - Badger - Sierras - 3 magnetic soundtracks - - edited., 1972 (Box 579)
  - Upward mobility - w.p. - pic. - 16mm. - black and white -, 1972. (Box 579)
  - S.O.F. August - master - pic. 16 mm. - voice & music track - 1972. (Box 579)
  - Steve Simon lecture #5 - orig. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 579)
  - Wedding festival - master material - w.p. - pic. - & soundtrack #1 -, 1972. (Box 579)
  - Profile - Charlie - w.p. (Box 579)
  - Directions '65 - ABC News. (Box 580)
  - Aerial footage of Oakland & San Francisco. (Box 719, Item 13)
  - Synanon in prison - Walter Cronkite - CBS -, March 16, 1966. (Box 580)
  - Miracle on the beach. (Box 580)
  - Hollywood yesterday. (Box 580)
  - General Electric Theater Presents: Night Club (Box 580, Item 18)
  - Synanon group pic. -, 1962. (Box 719, Item 16)
  - Blood. (Box 719, Item 11)
  - Detroit House -, 1972. (Box 580)
  - A/V Oakland School. (Box 719, Item 15)
  - Aerial footage of ranch & bay. (Box 719, Item 10)
  - Instant guide to Synanon. (Box 719, Item 1)
  - Man of sorrows -, 1970. (Box 580)
  - Public service spot - Natalie Wood, Chuck Connors. (Box 719, Item 3)
  - [Untitled reel - super 8 mm]. (Box 719, Item 2)
  - Or die - 18 min. - black and white. (Box 719, Item 8)
  - Narcotic addicts fight habit - interview with CED -, 1959. (Box 580)
  - Synanon commercial. (Box 719, Item 9)
  - Aerial footage of bay & ranch. (Box 580)
  - Ground breaking - w.p. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Synanon on film -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Synanon the people ranch -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Mobile rental unit - w.p. - outs - pic. -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Wedding. (Box 581)
  - Lighting with quartz. (Box 581)
  - Egg eating - orig. - outs. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Badger trucking - w.p. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Thickened light day - orig. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Oakland trip - orig. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Bill Stern on Lew Irwin reports. (Box 581)
  - Synanon at 1351. (Box 581)
  - Cardboard as as if - w.p. - outtakes - pic. -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Synanon wedding festival -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - People ranch ridge outs - pic.-, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Dance footage negative., 1962 (Box 581)
  - Synanon - 10th anniversary - orig. - printing master -, 1960. (Box 581)
  - NBC footage from 10th year celebration. (Box 581)
  - Badger trucking - orig. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Wedding - KGD orig. - [ceremony, dance, hoopla]. (Box 581)
  - Mechanical rolls. (Box 581)
  - NBC 10-year anniversary - Interviews at Ocean Front. (Box 581)
  - IDS - Ruth Stein. (Box 581)
  - Industries move - orig. - outs. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 581)
  - Basketball game - orig. & w.p. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 582)
  - Children's summer camp - orig. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 582)
    CONTAINS PROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Special equipment will be required for viewing. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Digital reproduction of this film is available.
  - People ranch - w.p. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 582)
  - Experiments in living - orig. - pic. - mag -, 1972. (Box 582)
  - Chinatown must change now. (Box 582)
  - 4H Club - orig. - pic. -, 1972. (Box 582)
  - WC construction - orig. & w.p. pic. -, 1972. (Box 582)
  - 10th anniversary. (Box 582)
  - [Unmarked container]. (Box 582)
  - Harvey Synanon history lecture - A & B roll - orig. -, 1973. (Box 582)
  - People ranch - copyright & title - A & B roll - pic. -, 1973. (Box 582)
  - Tomales construction - wk print - pic. (Box 582)
  - Titles - copyright-1972 - orig. & color. w.p. - pic. -, 1973. (Box 582)
  - Synanon basic training #17. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training #12. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training #5. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training #7. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training #9. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training. (Box 583)
  - Resources & wedding festival. (Box 583)
  - Instant guide to Synanon. (Box 583)
  - Steve Simon on the Synanon game - SF - black and white -, 1972. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training #15. (Box 583)
  - People business. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training #10. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training #18. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training. (Box 583)
  - People ranch. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training #16. (Box 583)
  - Instant guide to Synanon -, 1973. (Box 583)
  - Synanon basic training #6. (Box 583)
  - Teen game -, 1967. (Box 584)
  - Triptych - Bill Wagner. (Box 584)
  - The people ranch. (Box 584)
  - [Untitled video master tape]. (Box 584)
  - Art film. (Box 584)
  - Treasure from the sea. (Box 584)
  - People ranch. (Box 584)
  - People ranch - SM copy. (Box 584)
  - Children's game - the heritors / The inheritors -, 1967. (Box 584)
  - People ranch. (Box 585)
  - [Untitled video master tape]. (Box 585)
  - Cop out - new clue -, 1967. (Box 585)
  - [Untitled video master tape]. (Box 585)
  - Synanon - KGO - TV news film. (Box 585)
  - Triptych. (Box 585)
  - Wedding. (Box 586)
  - Service station crew game - reel 1 - - Tomales Bay - with script., January 30, 1967 (Box 586)